LIBE word expansion plugin:

This plugin enables you to create word expansions (different explanations of a specific word) that can be integrated within activities of a Moodle course/quizzes. The plugin includes a learner model that can be initialised through results from domain specific quizzes and questionnaires. The learner model is then used to provide word expansions to students that are tailored to their domain specific knowledge, such as their ability level (high, medium, low). 

To provide the word expansions you need to complete and import the following 2 csv files to the corresponding Moodle database tables. The files are placed in the database-import-files directory of the libe-personalised-word-expansion plugin:

1.	mdl_pe_libe_themes.csv: This csv file includes information about the abilities/skills addressed by your courses.
2.	mdl_pe_glossary.csv: This csv file includes information about words that can be expanded. You need to add your own word explanations to course activities as needed.

To integrate the word expansions within your Moodle exercise you need to include the JavaScript file local_pe_libecourses.js in the field Within Head in:
Site administration->Appearance->Additional HTML

<script src="http://<your domain name>/moodle/local/libe-personalised-word-expansion/local_pe_libecourses.js" type="text/
javascript"></script>

Then, the following css code has to be added in the field Custom CSS in:
Site administration->Appearance->Themes-><Your theme>->Custom CSS and JS


span.dropt {
      position: relative;
}

span.dropt span {
        display: none;
        color: #000;
}

span.dropt:hover span {
        position: absolute;
        display: inline;
        top: 0px;
        left: 0px;
        right: 0px;
        width: auto;
        margin: auto;
	padding: 5px;
	border-radius: 10px;
	background: #fff;
	background: -moz-linear-gradient(#fff, #999);
	background: -webkit-linear-gradient(#fff, #999);
	background: -o-linear-gradient(#fff, #999);
        z-index: 99999;
}



Finally, you have to add the following code to the quiz activity of your course, which evokes a mouse-over window that contains the word explanation:

<span class="dropt" onmouseover="word_expansion('<word to be explained>', 'demo1')" title="<word to be explained>" style="color: #fd8224;">word to be explained<span id="demo1">Pop-up text</span></span>


The plugin was developed as part of the LIBE project (Supporting Lifelong Learning with Inquiry-Based Education) that was funded by the European Commission.